Macbeth Gallery
Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
- Correspondence Files, 1838-1968, n.d., Series 1:; (Box 1-95, 163-164, OV 165; 96.2 linear feet)
  - Correspondence, 1838-1968, n.d., 1.1:
    - Failing, Henrietta E. and Mary F. Failing (2590), 1912-1937 (Box 34)
    - Failing, Henrietta H., 1924-1937 (Box 34)
    - Fairbanks, Avard (NMc44), 1928 (Box 34)
    - Fairbanks, Charles Mason (NMc6), 1910, 1912 (Box 34)
    - Fairchild, Benjamin T. (2590), 1928 (Box 34)
    - Fairchild, Helen L. (Mrs. Charles S.; 2590), 1895-1923, n.d. (Box 34)
    - Fairchild, Jarvis R., 1926 (Box 34)
    - Fangel, Henry (NMc6), 1894 (Box 34)
    - Farber, Mrs. M. P., 1913 (Box 34)
    - Faris, J. T., 1913 (Box 34)
    - Farley, [Agnes], 1906-ca. 1909 (Box 34)
    - Farley, Laura A. (Mrs. Frederick Augustus; 2590), 1939-1944 (Box 34)
    - Farmers' Loan and Trust Company, 1911-1926 (Box 34)
    - Farnham, Paulding, 1926 (Box 34)
    - Farnsworth, Jerry (NMc45), 1933 (Box 34)
    - Farr, Daniel H., 1914-1919, 1925-1928 (Box 34)
    - Farrall, Gertrude (Mrs. S. Clayton), 1942-1943 (Box 34)
    - Farrar, Susan R. (Mrs. H. C.), 1913, 1915, n.d. (Box 34)
    - Farrer, Henry (NMc6/NMc45), 1892-1901 (Box 34)
    - Fassett, Truman E. (NMc45), 1925-1926 (Box 34)
    - Fechin, Nicolai (NMc45), 1926, 1932 (Box 34)
    - Feiss, Paul L. (2590), 1916 (Box 34)
    - Feke Portraits (2590), 1918 (Box 34)
    - Felin, Charles F. (2590), 1920-1921 (Box 34)
    - Fenn, Harry (NMc6), ca. 1893 (Box 34)
    - Fenner, Evelyn K. (NMc6), 1896 (Box 34)
    - Fennessy, Andrew L. (2590), 1915-1916 (Box 34)
    - Fenton, Marion E. (2590), 1920-1926, n.d. (Box 34)
    - Ferargil Galleries (NMc45/2590), 1919-1953, (6 folders) (Box 34)
    - Ferdinand, John E., 1895-1898 (Box 34)
    - Ferguson, Nancy M. (NMc45), 1917-1920 (Box 34)
    - Ferris, Edythe (NMc45), 1932 (Box 34)
    - Ferris, Jean Léon Gérome (NMc6), 1893-1895, n.d., (includes illustrated letter) (Box 34)
    - Ferris, Richard (2590), 1920-1923 (Box 34)
    - Ferry, D. M., Jr. (NMc45/2590), 1914-1928, 1940 (Box 34)
    - Field, F. L., 1913, 1916 (Box 34)
    - Field, Hamilton Easter (NMc6/NMc45), 1904-1912, 1919, n.d. (Box 34)
    - Field, Mrs. L. B. (NMc6), ca. 1897 (Box 34)
    - Field, Marshall and Mrs. Field, 1925, 1946 (Box 34)
    - Fielding, Mantle (2590), 1920-1928 (Box 34)
    - Fifth Avenue Association (see also Cooke, Robert Grier; 2590), 1909-1933, (2 folders) (Box 34)
    - Fifth Avenue Protective Association (2590), 1926, 1932-1937 (Box 34)
    - Finck, Furman Joseph (2590), 1947-1955 (Box 35)
    - Findlay Galleries, Inc. (2590), 1903-1954, (4 folders) (Box 35)
    - Fine Arts (2590), 1932 (Box 35)
    - Fine Arts Gallery of San Diego, 1925-1946 (Box 35)
    - Fine Arts Journal, 1911-1916 (Box 35)
    - Fine Arts League, Los Angeles, California (2606/2607), 1913-1914, n.d. (Box 35)
    - Fine Arts Shop of Chicago, 1913-1914 (Box 35)
    - Fine Arts Studio & Book Shop, 1926 (Box 35)
    - Finnegan, Michael E., 1913-1914 (Box 35)
    - Finney, N. J., 1914 (Box 35)
    - Fisher, Anna S. (NMc45/2590), 1923-1926 (Box 35)
    - Fisher, Anton Otto (NMc6), 1909 (Box 35)
    - Fisher, Dorothy Canfield, 1932 (Box 35)
    - Fisher, Ellen B. Thayer (NMc6), 1906-1907 (Box 35)
    - Fisher, William A., 1895-1896 (Box 35)
    - Fisk, Mrs. F. N., 1914-1915 (Box 35)
    - Fiske, Charles A. (NMc6), ca. 1899 (Box 35)
    - Fisken, Jessie (NMc6), 1895-ca. 1903, n.d. (Box 35)
    - Fitch, George H., 1945 (Box 35)
    - Fitchburg Art Museum, 1937, 1958 (Box 35)
    - Fitler, Claude R. H. (NMc6/2590), 1916-1917 (Box 35)
    - Fitler, W. C. and Mrs. Fitler (NMc6/NMc45), 1892-ca. 1917 (Box 35)
    - Fitz, James L., 1913 (Box 35)
    - Fitzgerald, Harriet, 1945, 1957 (Box 35)
    - Fitzgerald, Harrington (NMc6/2590), 1901-1928 (Box 35)
    - Fitzgerald, James (NMc45), 1932-1933 (Box 35)
    - Fitzmaurice, Elsie, 1928 (Box 35)
    - Fitzpatrick, Herbert, 1926 (Box 35)
    - Flagg, Alice and Allard B. Flagg (2590), 1913-1926 (Box 35)
    - Flagg, Maurice I., 1914 (Box 35)
    - Flanagan, John, 1928 (Box 35)
    - Fleeson, Marian E., 1919 (Box 35)
    - Fleischman, Lawrence A. (2590), 1953-1955 (Box 35)
    - Fleischner, Mayer & Co., 1907 (Box 35)
    - Fleming, Dorion and Mrs. Fleming (2590), 1928, 1932 (Box 35)
    - Flint & Homer Co. Inc., 1924-1926 (Box 35)
    - Flint Institute of Arts (2590), 1928, 1941 (Box 35)
    - Flintoff, Laura (Mrs. Harrold R.; 2590), 1941-1944 (Box 35)
    - Florida Gulf Coast Art Center, Inc., 1949-1951 (Box 35)
    - Florida Society of Arts and Sciences (2590), 1925-1926 (Box 35)
    - Flynn's Express (2591), 1948-1956 (Box 35)
    - Fogg Art Museum (2591), 1915-1954 (Box 35)
    - Fogg, John S., 1924 (Box 35)
    - Folinsbee, John F. (NMc45/2591), 1914-1932 (Box 35)
    - Follett, Mrs. Ophie W. (2591), 1933-1946 (Box 35)
    - Folsom Galleries, 1911-1919 (Box 35)
    - Folsom, George C. (2591), ca. 1906-1916, (2 folders) (Box 35)
    - Foote, Louise (2591), 1924-1925 (Box 35)
    - Foote, Will Howe (NMc45/2591), 1914-1923 (Box 35)
    - Forbes, Edward W., 1908, 1948 (Box 35)
    - Force, Juliana R. (Mrs. W. B.; see also Whitney Museum of American Art; 2591), 1915-1920 (Box 35)
    - Ford, Blanche Butler (Mrs. E. L.; 2591), 1906-ca. 1910 (Box 35)
    - Ford, Henry and Mrs. Ford, 1914-1915, 1932 (Box 35)
    - Ford, J. Sawtelle (2591), 1914-1920 (Box 35)
    - Ford, Lauren, 1945 (Box 35)
    - Forehand, Frederic, 1914 (Box 35)
    - Fort Worth Art Association (2591), 1912-1913, 1932-1951 (Box 35)
    - Foster, Ben (NMc6/NMc45/2591), 1893-1926, (3 folders; includes an appreciation of William Macbeth, 8/21/17 and an illustrated letter, 8/8/18) (Box 35)
    - Foster Brothers, 1926 (Box 35)
    - Foster, Gerald (NMc45/2591), 1932-1937, n.d. (Box 35)
    - Foster, Joseph, Jr., 1918 (Box 35)
    - Fouke, Philip B. (see also box 164; 2591), 1913-1928, 1937, (2 folders) (Box 35)
    - Foulke, C. R. (2591), 1949 (Box 35)
    - Four Fountains, 1933 (Box 35)
    - Fournier, Alexis Jean (NMc6), 1907-1916 (Box 35)
    - Fowler, Naiomi (Mrs. W. C.), 1937-1949 (Box 35)
    - Fox, Charles K. and Ida L. Fox (2591), 1908-1924 (Box 35)
    - Fox, Edith Darrach (Mrs. Rector K., Jr.), 1933 (Box 35)
    - Fox, John (2591), 1953-1954 (Box 35)
    - Francis, Mary A. (Mrs. C. W.), 1917 (Box 35)
    - Franco, John, 1932-1933 (Box 35)
    - Frank, Aileen C. (Mrs. Erich P. Frank; 2591), 1937-1945 (Box 35)
    - Frank, Charles L. (see also box 164; 2591), 1916, 1919, 1933 (Box 35)
    - Frank K. M. Rehn, Inc., ca. 1892-1959, (2 folders) (Box 35)
    - Franklin Fisher & Associates (2591), 1948 (Box 35)
    - Franklin Spier Syndicate, 1926 (Box 35)
    - Franzen, August (NMc6/NMc45), 1914-1920, n.d. (Box 35)
    - Fraser, James E. (NMc6/NMc45/2591), 1910-1926 (Box 35)
    - Fraser, Nanette (NMc6), 1900-ca. 1902 (Box 35)
    - Fraser, O. W., 1932-1933 (Box 35)
    - Frazier, Mrs. James Carroll (2591), 1948 (Box 35)
    - Frazier, Kenneth (NMc6/NMc45), ca. 1893-1897, 1913, 1922 (Box 35)
    - Frederic B. Thomason, Inc., Insurance, 1895-1911, (4 folders) (Box 35)
    - Frederic B. Thomason, Inc., Insurance (see also box 164), 1912-1925, (32 folders) (Box 36)
    - Frederic B. Thomason, Inc., Insurance, 1926-1952, (29 folders) (Box 37)
    - Frederic B. Thomason, Inc., Insurance, 1953-1957, (2 folders) (Box 38)
    - Frederick, Frank F. (NMc45), 1911-1912, 1926 (Box 38)
    - Frederic Frazier, Inc. (2591), 1937 (Box 38)
    - Frederick Keer's Sons, 1906-1917 (Box 38)
    - Frederick Keppel & Co., Inc. (NMc57/2604), 1893-1937, n.d., (4 folders) (Box 38)
    - Frederick Loeser & Co. (2606), 1895, 1911-1920, n.d. (Box 38)
    - Freeman, Clayton E. (2591), 1945-1946 (Box 38)
    - Freeman, Marjorie W. (2591), 1932-1943 (Box 38)
    - Freeman, Percy R. (2591), 1924-1926 (Box 38)
    - Freer, Charles Lang (2591), 1893-1919 (Box 38)
    - French & Company, Inc. (2591), 1928, 1943-1956 (Box 38)
    - French, Daniel Chester (NMc46), 1911-1926 (Box 38)
    - French Gallery, 1895-1911, 1926-1928 (Box 38)
    - French, Pauline, 1924 (Box 38)
    - Freyermuth, F. C. and Mrs. Freyermuth (2591), 1921-1928 (Box 38)
    - Frick Art Reference Library (2591-2592), 1923-1958, (3 folders) (Box 38)
    - Frick, Henry Clay, 1895, 1899 (Box 38)
    - Fridenberg, Robert (Robert Fridenberg, Inc.; 2592), 1917, 1928-1939 (Box 38)
    - Friedmans' (2592),1922-1923 (Box 38)
    - Friends of American Art (see also Art Institute of Chicago), 1911-1915, 1921 (Box 38)
    - Friends of Art Association, Omaha, Nebraska, 1916-1918, n.d. (Box 38)
    - Fries, C. A. (NMc6/NMc46), 1912-1914 (Box 38)
    - Frieseke, Frederick C. (NMc6/NMc44/NMc46/NMc47/2592), ca. 1910-1939, (8 folders) (Box 38)
    - Frieseke, Frederick C., Estate (NMc6/NMc44/NMc46/NMc47/2592), 1939-1940, (2 folders) (Box 38)
    - Frieseke, Frederick C., Estate, and Sarah Ann Frieseke (NMc6/NMc44/NMc46/NMc47/2592), 1941-1956 (Box 38)
    - Frink, Francis G. (2592), 1928-1933 (Box 38)
    - Frink, Lillian J. (Mrs. William P.; 2592), 1916-1920, 1937-1940 (Box 38)
    - Frishmuth, Harriet Whitney (NMc46), 1911-1925 (Box 38)
    - Fritter, Mrs. W. C., 1913 (Box 38)
    - Fritz, Leonora V. (Mrs. E. B.), 1928 (Box 38)
    - Fromkes, Maurice (NMc46/2592), 1918-1925, (2 folders) (Box 38)
    - Frossard, Anna A., 1899-1905 (Box 38)
    - Frossard, Ed and Mrs. Frossard, 1898, 1909-1921 (Box 38)
    - Frost, A. B. (2592), 1919, 1923 (Box 38)
    - Frothingham, Elisabeth W. and John Frothingham (2592), 1917-1928 (Box 38)
    - Fuchs, Emil (NMc46), 1921-1928 (Box 38)
      (includes a letter to Fuchs from Isamu Noguchi, 12/1/26)
    - Fuessnich, F. W., 1942-1945 (Box 38)
    - Fuller, Arthur and Constance Fuller, 1915-1916, 1932, 1937 (Box 38)
    - Fuller, Lucy Derby (Mrs. S. Richard; 2592), 1918 (Box 38)
    - Fuller, Mrs. M. A., 1928 (Box 38)
    - Fuller, Mary (Mrs. George; NMc6), 1910-1914, 1932, n.d. (Box 38)
    - Fullick, Elizabeth (NMc6), 1900-1901, 1914 (Box 38)
    - Fullwood, A. Henry (NMc6), 1901-1902 (Box 38)
    - Furniss, Ruth MacFarland (2592), 1915, 1923 (Box 38)
    - F, Illegible and Unidentified, 1895-1949, n.d. (Box 38)
    - F, Miscellaneous: Fab-Fan (2589-2590), 1898-1950 (Box 38)
    - F, Miscellaneous: Far-Fay (2589-2590), 1898-1952 (Box 38)
    - F, Miscellaneous: Fe (2589-2590), 1898-1950 (Box 38)
    - F, Miscellaneous: Fic-Fin (2589-2590), 1901-1955 (Box 38)
    - F, Miscellaneous: Fir-Fit (2589-2590), 1899-1953 (Box 38)
    - F, Miscellaneous: Fl (2589-2590), 1895-1954 (Box 39)
    - F, Miscellaneous: Fog-Ford (2589-2590), 1899-1951 (Box 39)
    - F, Miscellaneous: Fore-Fox (2589-2590), ca. 1899-1953 (Box 39)
    - F, Miscellaneous: Fra-Fre (2589-2590), 1895-1951 (Box 39)
    - F, Miscellaneous: Fric-Frin (2589-2590), 1896-1963 (Box 39)
    - F, Miscellaneous: Fro-Fy (2589-2590), 1896-1956 (Box 39)
    - G. Lieber Company, 1905-1916, 1932, 1940 (Box 39)
    - G. P. Putnam's Sons, 1917-1924, 1956 (Box 39)
    - Gadsden, Helen T. (2593), 1921 (Box 39)
    - Gaertner, Carl (NMc49/2593), 1919, 1946-1953, (3 folders; includes illustrated letter 2/14/48; 1952 includes catalog of Gaertner exhibition) (Box 39)
    - Gage, B. W. (2593), 1914-1924 (Box 39)
    - Gage, George E. (2593), 1909-1939, n.d., (14 folders) (Box 39)
    - Gage, Mabel C. (2593), 1916 (Box 39)
    - Gage, T. H. (2593), 1912-1925, n.d. (Box 39)
    - Gagliardo, Ruth (Mrs. D.), 1932-1933 (Box 39)
    - Gahan, Dorothy C. (Mrs. J. J.), 1925-1926 (Box 39)
    - Gaines, S. M. (2593), 1916-1937, (2 folders) (Box 39)
    - Gainesville Association of Fine Arts, 1926 (Box 39)
    - Gallagher, Sears (NMc47), 1916, 1932 (Box 39)
    - Gallatin, A. E. (2593), 1912-1924 (Box 39)
    - Gallatin, Goelet, 1926 (Box 39)
    - Gallatin, Mrs. R. Horace, 1921-1926 (Box 39)
    - Gallery (2593), 1932-1933 (Box 39)
    - Gallery, Inc. (2593), 1947-1951 (Box 39)
    - Gamble, John M. (2593), 1937-1943 (Box 39)
    - Garber, Daniel and Mary Franklin Garber (NMc6/NMc44/NMc46/NMc47/2593), 1902-1933, 1944, n.d., (5 folders; includes exhibition catalog, 1/23) (Box 39)
    - Gardin, Alice T. (NMc49), 1922-1923 (Box 39)
    - Gardiner, A. P., 1932, (includes photograph of Gardiner with one of his paintings) (Box 39)
    - Gardner Advertising Company, 1930-1932 (Box 39)
    - Gardner, Signa B. (2593), 1955 (Box 39)
    - Gargoyle Club, 1913 (Box 39)
    - Garretson, Dorothy B. (Mrs. James), 1913 (Box 39)
    - Garvan, Francis P. and Mrs. Garvan (2593-2594), 1916-1937, (4 folders) (Box 40)
    - Garvan, Francis P., Estate (2593-2594), 1939-1953 (Box 40)
    - Garvin, William C. (2594), 1918-1924, 1932 (Box 40)
    - Gasser, Henry and Joane (2594), 1947-1953 (Box 40)
    - Gates, Elizabeth H. (Mrs. C. O.; 2594), 1898-1926 (Box 40)
    - Gatterdam, Pascal M. and Susie E. Gatterdam (2594), 1921-1958 (Box 40)
    - Gatthold, Florence (2594), 1916-1918 (Box 40)
    - Gaul, Gilbert, 1919 (Box 40)
    - Gauley, Robert David (NMc6), ca. 1900 (Box 40)
    - Gause, Harlan Victor, 1898, 1913-1915 (Box 40)
    - Gay, Alexander and George R. Gay, 1949-1950 (Box 40)
    - Gay, Edward (NMc6), 1897-1907, 1918, n.d. (Box 40)
    - Gay, George A. (2594), 1909-1926, 1932, (2 folders) (Box 40)
    - Gaylord, Elizabeth (Box 40)
    - Gebelein, George C., 1923-1933 (Box 40)
    - Geier, Paul, 1945-1946 (Box 40)
    - Gellatly, John (2594), 1912-1925 (Box 40)
    - Genth, Lillian (NMc6), 1903-1914, 1923-1924 (Box 40)
    - Gentner, Philip J. (2594; see also Smith, Amy and Frank C. Smith, Jr.), 1919-1926, 1938-1942 (Box 40)
    - George E. Vernon & Co., 1920-1922 (Box 40)
    - George F. Of, Inc., 1903-1942 (Box 40)
    - George, G. E., 1919 (Box 40)
    - George Walter Vincent Smith Art Museum, 1945-1946 (Box 40)
    - Gerdes, Cecilia M. (Mrs. A. M.; 2594), 1923-1925 (Box 40)
    - Gerdts, William H., Jr. (2594), 1955 (Box 40)
    - Gerrity, Thomas, 1915-1926, 1937 (Box 40)
    - Gest, J. H., 1932-1933 (Box 40)
    - Gibb, Florence (Mrs. Walter; 2594), 1913-1925, n.d. (Box 40)
    - Gibb, Mrs. L. M., 1932-1933 (Box 40)
    - Gibbs, George (NMc47), 1926 (Box 40)
    - Gibson, Charles Dana, 1941 (Box 40)
    - Gibson, Mary (2594), 1937-1943 (Box 40)
    - Gibson, Richardson, 1926 (Box 40)
    - Gibson, William Hamilton (NMc7), 1892-1896, n.d. (Box 40)
    - Gibson, William Wallace, (2594), 1916-1957, (3 folders) (Box 40)
    - Gidding, Peggy R. (Mrs. Leonard H.), 1933 (Box 40)
    - Gifford, Frances E. and Robert Swain Gifford (NMc7/NMc49), 1892-1911, n.d. (Box 40)
    - Gihon, Albert D. (2594), 1916 (Box 40)
    - Gihon, Clarence Montfort (NMc7), 1900-ca. 1902, 1916 (Box 40)
    - Gilchrist, W. A., 1917 (Box 40)
    - Gilchrist, W. W., Jr. (NMc7/NMc48/2594), 1912-1925 (Box 40)
    - Gilhousen, A. A., 1925 (Box 40)
    - Gill, James D. (2594), 1895-1933, (2 folders) (Box 40)
    - Gill, Paul L. and Sue May Gill (NMc47/2594), 1925-1937, 1948 (Box 40)
    - Gillet, Helen Kent, 1939 (Box 40)
    - Gillet, Louis Bliss, 1926-1937 (Box 40)
    - Gillette, William, 1919, 1926 (Box 40)
    - Gimbel Brothers, 1913-1926, 1948 (Box 40)
    - Girardeau, Adèle P. H. (Mrs. John Ferguson; 2594), 1944-1945 (Box 40)
    - Glackens, Edith and William J. Glackens (NMc48), 1913-1923 (Box 40)
    - Gladding, Nelson A., 1917-1932 (Box 40)
    - Gleitsmann, Glenna and Raphael Gleitsmann (2594), 1947-1953, (5 folders; includes catalog of Gleitsmann exhibition, April-May 1951) (Box 40)
    - Glover, Frederick W. (NMc7), 1912 (Box 40)
    - Gloversville Intercultural League (2594), 1947 (Box 40)
    - Goddard, Ralph B. (NMc7), 1894-1895 (Box 40)
    - Goeben, W. C., 1923-1937, 1947 (Box 40)
    - Goerck, Lewis W. (2594), 1917-1922 (Box 40)
    - Goldberg, Albert, 1925, ca. 1936 (Box 40)
    - Goldsmith Brothers, 1913-1924 (Box 40)
    - Goldsmith, Morton R. (2594), 1937, 1953-1955 (Box 40)
    - Golinkin, J. W. (NMc49), 1933 (Box 40)
    - Goltz, Walter (2594), 1916 (Box 40)
    - Gooch, Mrs. C. M., 1932-1933 (Box 40)
    - Gooch, Mrs. M. A., 1924 (Box 40)
    - Good, Robert, 1931-1933 (Box 40)
    - Goodale, John McG., 1902-1908 (Box 40)
    - Goodhue, F. Abbot, 1949-1956, n.d. (Box 40)
    - Goodlatte, Robert K., 1920-1924 (Box 40)
    - Goodlett, R. F., 1913-1914 (Box 40)
    - Goodman-Walker Inc. (2594), 1932-1941 (Box 40)
    - Goodman, William O. (2594), 1911-1917 (Box 40)
    - Goodman, Laurence B., 1956-1957 (Box 40)
    - Goodrich, Lloyd (2594), 1937 (Box 40)
    - Goodspeed's Book Shop (2594), 1914-1926, 1932-1933, (2 folders) (Box 40)
    - Goodwin, Adda Frances and Helen M. Goodwin (NMc48/2594/2595), 1922-1924 (Box 40)
    - Goodwin, Arthur Clifton (NMc7/NMc48), 1904-1922 (Box 40)
    - Goodwin, Elizabeth Sage (Mrs. E. L.), 1911-1916, n.d. (Box 40)
    - Goodwin, Milan H. (2595), 1913-1917 (Box 40)
    - Goodyear, A. Conger (2595), 1921-1953 (Box 40)
    - Gordan, Eleanor Kinzie, 1913 (Box 40)
    - Gorham Company (2595), 1910-1922, 1943-1944, (2 folders) (Box 40)
    - Gorson, A. H., 1914-1933 (Box 41)
    - Gotthold, Florence (NMc48), 1917-1919, n.d. (Box 41)
    - Gottschalk, E., 1915 (Box 41)
    - Gottwald, F. C., 1913 (Box 41)
    - Gould, Carl F. and Dorothy Fay Gould, 1913-1916, n.d. (Box 41)
    - Gould, Eleanor Kinzie, 1913 (Box 41)
    - Goupil Gallery, 1922 (Box 41)
    - Gove, S. H., 1923 (Box 41)
    - Grace Borgenicht Gallery, 1953 (Box 41)
    - Grady, George, 1932-1950 (Box 41)
    - Graecan, Edmund, ca. 1911-1933, n.d. (Box 41)
    - Graham, Hinkley & Co. (W. H. Lake), 1921-1927 (Box 41)
    - Graham, Horace Sague and Lois H. Graham, 1937 (Box 41)
    - Graham, Robert C. (2595), 1957 (Box 41)
    - Granberry, Imogene and W. H. Granberry (2595), 1895-1914 (Box 41)
    - Grand Central Art Galleries (NMc48/2595), 1923-1953, (9 folders) (Box 41)
    - Grand Rapids Art Association (2595), 1913-1932, 1947 (Box 41)
    - Grandin, E. B. (2595), ca. 1912-1916 (Box 41)
    - Grandin, Florence, 1924-1925 (Box 41)
    - Grant, David, 1933 (Box 41)
    - Grant, Gordon (NMc48), 1932, 1937 (Box 41)
    - Grant, Lawrence (NMc7/NMc49), 1912-1913 (Box 41)
    - Grant, Rosemary (Mrs. Alan), 1943-1944 (Box 41)
    - Granville-Smith, Walter (NMc48), 1917-1933 (Box 41)
    - Gravatt, Sara (Mrs. W. Loyall, Jr.; 2595), 1937 (Box 41)
    - Graves, Abbott (NMc48), 1932-1933 (Box 41)
    - Graves, Algernon (2595), 1916-1919, (2 folders) (Box 41)
    - Gravesande, Charles Storm van (NMc7), 1894-1899 (Box 41)
    - Gray, David (2595), 1918-1932, (3 folders) (Box 41)
    - Gray, Mary (NMc48), 1933 (Box 41)
    - Gray, Samuel B., 1922 (Box 41)
    - Greater Hotel Gibson, 1932-1933 (Box 41)
    - Greeley, Eva R., 1917 (Box 41)
    - Green, Bernard I. (NMc48), 1933 (Box 41)
    - Green, Charles A., 1909-1922 (Box 41)
    - Green, Estelle Bakewell (2595), 1921-1922 (Box 41)
    - Green, F. (NMc7), ca. 1902 (Box 41)
    - Green, Samuel M., 1950-1951 (Box 41)
    - Greenbaum, Wolff & Ernst (2595), 1916 (Box 41)
    - Greene, Albert Van Nesse, 1925 (Box 41)
    - Greene, Mary Amory (2595), 1906, 1923-1932 (Box 41)
    - Greene, Edward R., 1912-1913 (Box 41)
    - Greenshields, Edward (2595), 1936 (Box 41)
    - Greenwich Country Day School, 1932 (Box 41)
    - Greer, W. Robert, 1917 (Box 41)
    - Gregg, James, 1925-1926 (Box 41)
    - Gregory, Anne (NMc7), 1892-1893 (Box 41)
    - Gregory, Dorothy Lake, 1932-1933 (Box 41)
    - Gregory, Elizabeth J., 1902 (Box 41)
    - Gregory, Grace V. (NMc7), 1895-1896, n.d. (Box 41)
    - Gregory, John (NMc7), 1911 (Box 41)
    - Greyer, W. A. (2595), 1895-1896 (Box 41)
    - Grieumard, Louis C., 1917, 1923-1924 (Box 41)
    - Griffin, A. C., 1933 (Box 41)
    - Griffith, Mary C. (enclosing 2 letters from Raffaelli), 1932, n.d. (Box 41)
    - Griffith, Raymond, 1939 (Box 41)
    - Griggs, Mary C. (2595), 1898-1908 (Box 41)
    - Grimm, Dorothy S. (Mrs. William; 2595), 1956-1960 (Box 41)
    - Griscom, Acton, 1925-1926 (Box 41)
    - Griscom, William Morris, Jr., 1918, 1925 (Box 41)
    - Griswold, A. W. (2595), 1915-1919 (Box 41)
    - Griswold, Mrs. C., 1913 (Box 41)
    - Griswold, Casimir Clayton (NMc7), 1892 (Box 41)
    - Griswold, Florence, 1919 (Box 41)
    - Grolier Craft Press, Inc., 1923-1926 (Box 41)
    - Groll, Albert L (NMc7/NMc49/2595), 1902-1933, 1946 (Box 41)
    - Groom, Emily (NMc49), 1914-1915, 1926 (Box 41)
    - Groome, Esther M. (NMc49/2595), 1912-1925 (Box 41)
    - Gross, Herman and Hildegard Rath (Mrs. Herman Gross; 2595), 1948-1953 (Box 41)
    - Gross, Juliet White (NMc49), 1911-1922 (Box 41)
    - Groves, Mrs. John G. (2595), 1916 (Box 41)
    - Grunewald, F. L., Jr., 1913-1917, 1933 (Box 41)
    - Gruppe, Charles, 1956 (Box 41)
    - Gruppe, Charles Paul and Emile A. Gruppe (NMc7/NMc49/2595), 1894-1937, n.d. (Box 41)
    - Guarino, Salvatore Anthony (NMc7), 1908-1916 (Box 41)
    - Guerard, Fanny R. (2595), 1921-1922 (Box 41)
    - Guérin, Jules (NMc7/NMc49), 1892-1897, 1915-1916 (Box 41)
    - Guernsey, Emmeline, 1949 (Box 41)
    - Guerry, Prosper, 1915-1924, 1933 (Box 41)
    - Guffey, Frank H., 1923-1924 (Box 41)
    - Guggenheim, Mrs. Benjamin, 1913-1916, 1926 (Box 41)
    - Guggenheim, Murray, 1917 (Box 41)
    - Gugler, Frida (NMc7/NMc49), 1909-1915 (Box 41)
    - Guild of Boston Artists (George Sloane), 1916-1942 (Box 41)
    - Gumplo-Ainslie Galleries, Inc., 1932 (Box 41)
    - Gunsaulus, F. W., 1905-1910 (Box 41)
    - Gunther, C. F., 1914-1917 (Box 41)
    - Gutman, Mrs. Monroe C., 1923 (Box 41)
    - Gutmann, Bernhard (NMc7/NMc49), 1913, 1926 (Box 41)
    - Gwathmey, Betsy C. (Mrs. Archibald B.), 1932 (Box 41)
    - G, Illegible, 1903-1953 (Box 41)
    - G, Miscellaneous: G.-Gan (2592-2593), 1903-1953 (Box 41)
    - G, Miscellaneous: Garb-Garr (2592-2593), 1896-1954 (Box 42)
    - G, Miscellaneous: Gart-Gaz (2592-2593), 1909-1956 (Box 42)
    - G, Miscellaneous: Ge (2592-2593), 1895-1953 (Box 42)
    - G, Miscellaneous: Gh-Gild (2592-2593), 1898-1947 (Box 42)
    - G, Miscellaneous: Gile-Give (2592-2593), 1896-1955 (Box 42)
    - G, Miscellaneous: Gl (2592-2593), 1899-1953 (Box 42)
    - G, Miscellaneous: God-Gon (2592-2593), 1896-1960 (Box 42)
    - G, Miscellaneous: Good-Goodyear (2592-2593), 1899-1956 (Box 42)
    - G, Miscellaneous: Gor-Gow (2592-2593), 1898-1956 (Box 42)
    - G, Miscellaneous: Gra (2592-2593), 1896-1957 (Box 42)
    - G, Miscellaneous: Grea-Green (2592-2593), 1910-1953 (Box 42)
    - G, Miscellaneous: Greenb-Grey (2592-2593), 1896-1948 (Box 42)
    - G, Miscellaneous: Gri (2592-2593), 1894-1953 (Box 42)
    - G, Miscellaneous: Gro (2592-2593), 1900-1954 (Box 42)
    - G, Miscellaneous: Gru-Gugg (2592-2593), 1895-1954 (Box 42)
    - G, Miscellaneous: Gui-Gw (2592-2593), 1898-1945 (Box 42)
    - H. J. Heinz Company, 1927 (Box 42)
    - H. M. Green & Co., 1956-1957 (Box 42)
    - H. Mallon & Cie, 1913 (Box 42)
    - H. T. Carey & Co. (2577), 1928-1933, (2 folders) (Box 42)
    - H. W. Johns-Manville Co. (2602), 1914-1916 (Box 42)
    - Hackett, Helen, 1932, 1946-1948 (Box 42)
    - Hackley Art Gallery, 1913-1937, 1946 (Box 42)
    - Hadden, Mary B. (Mrs. D. P.; 2597), 1914-1932 (Box 42)
    - Hafner, Mark, 1924-1932 (Box 42)
    - Hague, Maurice Stewart (NMc7), 1909, 1911 (Box 42)
    - Haher, Mary C. (Mrs. James H.; 2597), 1945 (Box 42)
    - Haight, G. B. and Mrs. Haight (2597), 1895-1899, 1914-1924 (Box 42)
    - Hailman, George L. (2597), 1937 (Box 42)
    - Hailman, Johanna K. Woodwill (NMc7), 1911-ca. 1915 (Box 42)
    - Halaby Galleries, 1923-1927 (Box 42)
    - Hale, Lillian W. (Mrs. Philip L.; NMc49), 1925-1926 (Box 42)
    - Hale, Mary (Mrs. William; NMc49), 1921, 1927 (Box 42)
    - Hale, Richard W., 1925 (Box 42)
    - Haley & Steele, 1923-1925 (Box 42)
    - Hall, Carl (2597), 1949-1953 (Box 42)
    - Hall, Frank M., 1919-1926 (Box 42)
    - Hall, Frederic G. (2597), 1915, 1922, n.d. (Box 42)
    - Hall, Harriet B. (Mrs. Louis P.), 1925-1926 (Box 42)
    - Hall, M. A. (also Mrs. Charles T. Kountze and Mrs. Halleck Rose), 1914-1916 (Box 42)
    - Hall, Standish (2597), 1937 (Box 42)